chartnexus.com 2017-12-01

# Privacy Policy Page :: ChartNexus® - Chart Your Success

### CHARTNEXUS® PRIVACY POLICY::

#### OVERVIEW

Welcome to the website of ChartNexus® (http://www.chartnexus.com) ("Website"). Throughout the Website, we may ask for information or collect information from you. We respect this personally identifiable information ("Personal Information"). We recognize the importance of the Personal Information and is committed to protecting this information. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more and to understand our practices on using this Personal Information. If you still have any doubts or enquiries about any privacy issues, please [contact us](http://www.chartnexus.com/support/contactus.php#cform). 

This Privacy Policy applies to all of our services available through the Website. By using this Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

#### CHOICE

You may choose to provide us your personal information. In most cases, you can access and use most of the services available through the Website. However, for certain areas/sections providing privilege offers, content and services, you may not be able to access them.

#### SECURITY

We intend to safeguard the Personal Information from unauthorized access or disclosure. No staffs or employees of ours will require account password from any user to reset your account in the event that the user has lost or forget his/her password. If any staff (even attempt to) solicit password from you, please [report to us](http://www.chartnexus.com/support/contactus.php#cform). 

#### ACCURACY & UPDATES

We are committed to provide your with excellent products and services. The Personal Information collected will enable us to understand you better thereby meeting your needs. It is important that we maintain accurate and up-to-date Personal Information of you. Should you need to update or correct that Personal Information, please [inform us](http://www.chartnexus.com/support/contactus.php#cform) or you may update the information through the forms provided. 

#### THIRD PARTY

In the Website or our email communication, we may provide links or references to third party sites; Third parties may offer you products or services through the Website, we are not responsible for the actions of these third parties as they retain total control over their websites, products or services. We do not, however, sell, share or rent the Personal Information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your consent.

#### COMMITMENT

Protecting privacy rights is an evolving area. We intend to update the Privacy Policy as best to our ability to reflect your demand and rights. If you have any feedback or comments regarding our policy, please [contact us](http://www.chartnexus.com/support/contactus.php#cform). 

#### PERSONAL DATA

ChartNexus Mastery Pte Ltd has your consent to contact you via email, sms and phone for any invitation to future events and promotions.

Last Revised/Reviewed : 23th Jul 2006.  
Revision : 1.2 

Past Revisions :

  * v1.0 \- Last revised 1st November 2004
  * v1.1 \- Last revised 3rd September 2005
